Osborne Family Papers
Osborne Family Papers
- Legal records
  - General
    - Husted,. S. to A. Wood and H. Ward: Mortgage, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1854 (Box 295)
    - Isham, J. and wife to T. Maxwell: Deed, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1846 (Box 295)
    - Jacobs, H.M.: Patents, Machine, 1860 (Box 295)
    - Jemison, A., Jr. and wife to T.M. Osborne: Mortgage, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1903 (Box 295)
    - Johnson, R.G. and wife to A.G. Johnson: Deed, Tompkins County, N.Y., 1869 (Box 295)
    - Jones, A.E. to Cayuga County Savings Bank: Mortgage, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1890 (Box 295)
    - Jones, C. and wife to A. Cornwell: Mortgage, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1842 (Box 295)
    - Jordan, E. to B. Kerby: Indenture, 1794 (Box 295)
    - Keirby, B.: Will, 1778 (Box 295)
    - Kerby, N. to E. Kerby: Guardianship bond for son, Bestcome, 1786 (Box 295)
    - For Kirby, B. (deceased): Administrative appointment, 1838 (Box 295)
    - Kirby, B. to others: Leases, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1824-1827 (Box 295)
    - Kirby, E. with W.P. Wright: Agreement, 1870 (Box 295)
    - Kirby, S.: Land survey, 1784 (Box 295)
    - Kirby and Osborne with D.M. Osborne & Co.: Patents, Harvester, 1856-1866 (Box 296)
    - Kirby and Osborne with Wells, Blood and Blood Patents, Harvester, 1858 (Box 296)
    - Kniffin, N.: Will, 1859 (Box 296)
    - Lehigh Valley Railroad to T.M. Osborne: Lease, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1905-1917 (Box 296)
    - Leail and Archer to Auburn Savings Institution: Mortgage, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1852 (Box 296)
    - Lelover, E. to C. Patten: Deed, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1873 (Box 296)
    - Lemmon, H.N. and others to T.M. Osborne: Deeds, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1889-1927 (Box 296)
    - Liveter, T. to D. and S. Littser: Deed, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1843 (Box 296)
    - Lot Maps: Miscellaneous, undated (Box 296)
    - Lowell, S.: Affidavits, 1903 (Box 296)
    - McDonough, M. to T.M. Osborne: Mortgage, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1897 (Box 296)
    - McKain, M.E. to T.M. Osborne: Deed, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1905 (Box 296)
    - McNeil, H.C. to E.W. Osborne: Deed, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1905 (Box 296)
    - Macomber, S. to L. Macomber: Mortgage, Wayne County, N.Y., 1838 (Box 296)
    - Mallory, J. to H. Sheldon: Lease, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1852 (Box 296)
    - Marsh, J.S.: Patents, Harvester, 1863-1869; 2 folders (Box 296)
    - Mathews, S.J. and wife to D.M. Osborne: Deed, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1872 (Box 296)
    - Means, J.H.: Patents, Mechanical rake, 1862 (Box 296)
    - Memoranda of Judgments, 1843-1845 (Box 296)
    - Merriman, C. to P. Munro: Mortgage, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1857-1858 (Box 296)
    - Middlemiss, H.S.: Affidavit, 1913 (Box 296)
    - Miller, B. to H. Treat: Bond, 1846 (Box 296)
    - Miller, D. and wife to E. Wales: Mortgage, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1852 (Box 296)
    - Miller, S. and others to the George Junior Republic: Deeds, Tompkins County, N.Y., 1896-1901 (Box 296)
    - Miller, W.H.: Affidavit, 1907 (Box 296)
    - Moravia Oil Company with Owasco Valley Oil Company: Agreement, 1865 (Box 296)
    - Moses, W.J. to D.M. Osborne: Deed, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1872 (Box 296)
    - Mosher, V.: Patents, Railroad axles, 1854 (Box 296)
    - Mount Royal, Putnam County, Fla.: Lot maps and surveys, 1883 (Box 296)
    - Munson, O. with A. Miller: Covenant, 1849 (Box 296)
    - Mykoff, P.C. and wife to L.D. Harmon: Deeds, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1854 (Box 296)
    - New York and Santa Fe Mining Company of Nevada: Articles of Incorporation, 1865 (Box 296)
    - New York Central Railroad Company to T.M. Osborne Memorial Committee and City of Auburn: Lease, Cayuga County, N.Y. (Box 296)
    - New York State: Legislation, Miscellaneous, 1906-1921 (Box 296)
    - New York State Commission to Investigate State Prisons:. Executive order, 1913 (Box 296)
    - Noyes, L. to D. Lester and others: Bond, 1842 (Box 296)
    - Osborne, J.A.: Will and probate, 1888-1936 (Box 296)
    - Osborne, A.: Will, 1891-1914 (Box 296)
    - Osborne, D.M.
      - Miscellaneous, 1864-1865 (Box 296)
      - Agreement with VanAuken and Doolittle, 1884 (Box 296)
      - Bond to Equitable Life Assurance Society, 1873-1888 (Box 296)
      - Estate, 1886-1906 (Box 296)
      - Guardianship appointment for F.H. Osborne and A.J. Osborne, 1847 (Box 296)
      - Leases to others, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1873-1888 (Box 297)
      - Lot maps, Utica, N.Y. properties, 1875 (Box 297)
      - Mortgages, Cayuga County, N.Y.
        - to Cayuga County Savings Bank, 1873-1880 (Box 297)
        - to J.S. Seymour, 1879 (Box 297)
      - Power of attorney to D. Wright, 1872-1874 (Box 297)
      - Will and probate, 1889-1896 (Box 297)
    - Osborne, D.M. and wife
      - Deed: to New York, West Shore & Buffalo Railway Co., Oneida County, N.Y., 1882 (Box 297)
      - Mortgage, Cayuga County: to E. Leonard, 1872 (Box 297)
    - Osborne, D.M., H. Barker and L. Baldwin: Articles of copartnership, 1852 (Box 297)
    - Osborne, D.M., J.H. Osborne and O.H. Burdick: Articles of copartnership, 1866 (Box 297)
    - D.M. Osborne & Co.
      - Articles of copartnership, 1858-1866 (Box 297)
      - Contracts: Manufacture and sale of harvesters, 1857-1860 (Box 297)
      - Patents, miscellaneous, 1858-1867 (Box 297)
    - Osborne, D.M. II, 1886-1923 (Box 297)
    - Osborne, D.: Will, 1912 (Box 297)
    - Osborne, E.
      - Miscellaneous, 1891-1906 (Box 297)
      - Agreement: with C. Gilbert, 1909 (Box 297)
      - Leases, 1887-1901 (Box 297)
      - Mortgage release, Oneida County, N.Y., 1887-1891 (Box 297)
      - Schedule of legal services with Underwood, Storke & Seward, 1902-1906 (Box 297)
      - Will and probate, 1881-1911 (Box 297)
    - Osborne, E. and others
      - Deed, Cayuga County, N.Y.: to D.R. Alward and others, 1888 (Box 297)
      - Power of attorney
        - to C.F. Baldwin, 1894 (Box 297)
        - to T.M. Osborne, 1891-1894 (Box 297)
      - Mortgages, Oneida County, N.Y.: to the Savings Bank of Utica, 1887; 1902 (Box 297)
    - Osborne, F.: Will and probate, 1886-1887 (Box 297)
    - Osborne, J.: Land survey, 1838 (Box 297)
    - Osborne, J.F., 1904-1914 (Box 297)
    - Osborne, L.
      - Miscellaneous, 1926-1949 (Box 297)
      - Contract: with M. Dolm, 1962 (Box 297)
      - Deeds, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1927-1930 (Box 297)
      - Guardianship of R. Osborne, 1934-1949 (Box 297)
      - Power of attorney, 1928-1946 (Box 297)
    - Osborne, L.D.: Trust, 1927 (Box 297)
    - Osborne, R. to L. Osborne: Lease, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1942 (Box 297)
    - Osborne, T.M.
      - Miscellaneous, 1906-1926 (Box 297)
      - Agreements
        - Real estate
          - with P. Beardsley, 1908-1917 (Box 297)
          - with Town of Dryden, N.Y., 1905 (Box 297)
          - with Village of Freeville, N.Y., 1905 (Box 297)
          - with E. B. and H. J. Koon, 1912 (Box 297)
          - with J.F. Nagel, 1916 (Box 297)
        - Right of way: with New York Telephone Co., 1917 (Box 297)
        - Public Works: with W.J. Slaver, 1905 (Box 297)
      - Certificate of ownership: Oldsmobile, 1902 (Box 297)
      - Contracts
        - Miscellaneous: with J.A. Kilmer, 1908 (Box 298)
        - Film
          - with K.R. Bleeker, Inc., 1917 (Box 298)
          - with C.C. Hatchet and others, 1921 (Box 298)
          - with J. Haupt, 1917 (Box 298)
          - with Producers Security Corporation, 1921 (Box 298)
        - Publishing
          - with D. Appleton & Co., 1914 (Box 298)
          - with Lippincott Publishing Co., 1923 (Box 298)
      - Copyright, Adventures of a Green Dragon, 1908 (Box 298)
      - Deeds
        - Miscellaneous, 1909-1917 (Box 298)
        - Cayuga County, N.Y.
          - to E.M. Osborne, 1905 (Box 298)
          - to W. Payne, 1913 (Box 298)
          - to L.E. Springer, 1923 (Box 298)
          - to E. Volland, 1909 (Box 298)
      - Eviction notice: to E.R. Redhead, Auburn Sanitary Milk Co., Inc., 1921-1922 (Box 298)
      - Leases, 1848-1933 (Box 298)
      - Mortgages, Cayuga County, N.Y.
        - to Cayuga County Savings Bank, 1905 (Box 298)
        - to C.B. Wheeler, 1903 (Box 298)
      - Note to C. Osborne, 1919 (Box 298)
      - Power of attorney
        - to G.D. Boardman, 1915-1917 (Box 298)
        - to A.L. Devens, 1894 (Box 298)
        - to D.M. Osborne, 1913 (Box 298)
        - to E.W. Osborne, 1907 (Box 298)
        - to L. Osborne, 1923 (Box 298)
      - Stock Agreement: with E.R. Redhead and Cayuga County Dairy Co., Auburn, N.Y., 1917 (Box 298)
      - Wills, 1913-1915 (Box 298)
    - Osborne, T.M. and wife: Power of attorney to C.F. Baldwin, 1894 (Box 298)
    - Osborne, T.M. and others
      - Agreements
        - Real estate: with E. Osborne, 1886 (Box 298)
        - Retainer: with G.D. Boardman, 1915-1918 (Box 298)
      - Contract: with Industrial Construction Co., 1906 (Box 298)
      - Deed, Cayuga County, N.Y. to J. VanSickle, 1905 (Box 298)
      - Mortgage, Cayuga County, N.Y. to Monroe County Savings Bank, 1898-1904 (Box 298)
    - Osborne Family
      - Deeds
        - Wianno property, Barnstable, Barnstable County, Mass., 1912 (Box 298)
        - "The Wright Avenue Tract," Auburn, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1865-1903 (Box 298)
    - Owasco Valley Oil Company: Leases, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1865 (Box 298)
    - Owasco Valley Oil Company and Moravia Oil Co. with W.H. Johnson: Contract, 1865 (Box 298)
    - Park, J. Jr. and wife to J. Park: Mortgage, Westchester County, N.Y., 1821 (Box 298)
    - Parks, I. and wife to H. Smith: Mortgage, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1840 (Box 298)
    - Payne Property for Southern Central Railroad Co.; Appraisal, 1870 (Box 298)
    - Peabody, K.N.T. ("Katrina Trask"): Will, 1921 (Box 298)
    - J.H. Peacock Property, Cayuga County, N.Y.: Deeds, contracts, memoranda, 1870-1906 (Box 298)
    - Peabody, A.J.: Application for pardon, 1920-1927 (Box 298)
    - Peavy, A.J.: Pardon, 1927 (Box 298)
    - Pederson, S. to O.W. Guelick: Mortgage, Oneida County, N.Y., 1869 (Box 298)
    - Phelps, S. and wife to J. Swan: Deeds, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1810-1816 (Box 298)
    - T. Pomeroy to J. Alward: Lease, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1854 (Box 298)
    - Potts, G.: Patents, Copper lining of cylinders, 1853 (Box 298)
    - Raben-Levetzau, F.C.O.: Will, 1933 (Box 298)
    - Ransom, N.G. to F.A. Nelson: Deed, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1867 (Box 298)
    - Rattigan, C.F. with T.M. Osborne: Agreement, 1916 (Box 298)
    - Raymond, C.F: Estate settlement, 1912 (Box 298)
    - Reed, T. to B. and H. Weatherby: Referee's deed, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1878 (Box 298)
    - Rembert, W.P. to W.P. Wright: Deed, Putnam County, Fla., 1881 (Box 298)
    - Reynolds, A. and others to N. Alward: Bond, 1844 (Box 298)
    - Richardson, S.L. to J. Swan; Deed, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1818 (Box 298)
    - Robertson, A. to J. Whitely: Deed, Cayuga. County, N.Y., 1839 (Box 298)
    - Sant, C. and wife to J. VanDyne: Deed, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1854 (Box 299)
    - Scipio, N.Y.
      - Lot Description, undated (Box 299)
      - Warrants to collect school tax, 1822 (Box 299)
    - Searing, J.: Will, undated (Box 299)
    - Shea, C.P.: Parole, 1914 (Box 299)
    - Shoemaker, D. and wife to D.M. Osborne: Deed, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1880 (Box 299)
    - Sheldon, F. to B. Ashby: Deed, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1856 (Box 299)
    - Siveter, T. to J. Robee: Deed, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1845 (Box 299)
    - Smith, B.: Land survey, undated (Box 299)
    - Smith, E. to J. Borst: Mortgage, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1852 (Box 299)
    - Smith Property for the Southern Central Railroad Co.: Appraisal, 1870 (Box 299)
    - Southern Central Railroad Company: Articles of Incorporation, 1865 (Box 299)
    - Squire, G.L. with W.A. Kirby and D.M. Osborne: Agreement, Harvester patent, 1866 (Box 299)
    - Stafon, D. to D. Hunter: Deed, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1851 (Box 299)
    - Stanton, J. to A. Fitch.: Mortgage, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1855 (Box 299)
    - J.W. Steere and Son, Organ Company with First Universalist Church of Auburn, N.Y., 1913 (Box 299)
    - Stevens, W.: Will, 1854 (Box 299)
    - Stewart, A.: Application for Pardon, 1905 (Box 299)
    - Storrow, H.O. to T.M. Osborne: Deed, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1897 (Box 299)
    - Storrow, H.O.: Will, undated (Box 299)
    - Swan, Jonathan to S. Brush: Lease, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1825 (Box 299)
    - Swan, Jonathan: Will and probate, 1828 (Box 299)
    - Swan, John to Jonathan Swan: Deed, Oneida County, N.Y., 1809 (Box 299)
    - Swan, Joseph R. and wife to E.C. Marsh: Deed, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1836 (Box 299)
    - Swan, Joseph R. and wife to D. Wright: Power of attorney, 1842 (Box 299)
    - Tatum, H.V. to E.W. Osborne: Deed, Osterville, Mass., 1890 (Box 299)
    - Ten Eyck, F.G. to T.M. Osborne: Mortgage, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1912 (Box 299)
    - Thomas, D. and wife to S. Richardson: Quitclaim, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1815 (Box 299)
    - Thomas, R.W. and others to C.C. Dennis and others: Deed, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1842 (Box 299)
    - Thornton, F. to. R. Chamberlain: Mortgage, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1857 (Box 299)
    - Tousley, R. and wife to J. Swan: Deed, Seneca County, N.Y., 1815 (Box 299)
    - Townsend, H. to J. Earl: Mortgage, Steuben County, N.Y., 1836 (Box 299)
    - Townsend, W. to J. White: Mortgage, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1855 (Box 299)
    - Underhay, F.G.: Patents, Harvesters, 1853 (Box 299)
    - VanMiddlesworth, J. to H. VanMiddlesworth: Bond, 1841 (Box 299)
    - VanValkenburgh, J. to S. Goodwin: Mortgage, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1845 (Box 299)
    - Victory, H.L. to H.H. Victory: Mortgage, Oneida County, N.Y., 1902 (Box 299)
    - Voorhees, J. to S. Brown: Transfer of judgment, 1855 (Box 299)
    - Waddington, J. and others to F. Pell: Deed, New York City, 1824 (Box 299)
    - Ward, F.A. to L. Osborne: Deed, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1927 (Box 299)
    - Warden, A. and wife to C.C. Dennis and C.P. Wood: Deed, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1842 (Box 299)
    - Watrous, J. L.: with D.M. Osborne: Articles of copartnership, 1848 (Box 299)
    - Watts, J. to J. Swan: Deed, Oneida County, N.Y., 1808 (Box 299)
    - Weatherby, G. and wife to S. Swan: Deed, Allegheny County, N.Y., 1833 (Box 299)
    - Wendell, B.: Estate, 1921 (Box 299)
    - Wendell, J.: Estate, 1920 (Box 299)
    - Whaley, R. to C. Cuyler and E. Burnham: Mortgage, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1833 (Box 299)
    - Whiting, B. to R. DeGang: Mortgage, 1843 (Box 299)
    - Williams, L. and E. B. Koon to T.M. Osborne: Deed and title search, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1892-1903 (Box 299)
    - Williams, M. to G. Ashby: Deed, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1859 (Box 299)
    - Winegar, C.: Patents, Lime compound, 1859 (Box 299)
    - Wood, C.P. to D.M. Osborne: Mortgage, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1871-1898 (Box 299)
    - Wood, W. and wife to J. Swan: Deed, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1810 (Box 299)
    - Woodruff, Allen & Co.: Articles of copartnership, 1867 (Box 299)
    - Wright, D.
      - Miscellaneous, 1837-1872 (Box 299)
      - Agreements
        - Loan, to P. Clerkin, 1851 (Box 299)
        - Sharecropping, with E.D. Kirkpatrick, 1878 (Box 299)
      - Contract: with D. Peete, 1872 (Box 299)
      - Deed, Cayuga County, N.Y.: to M. J. Carroll, 1872 (Box 299)
      - Fees and costs: to U.S. Circuit Court Clerk, Utica, N.Y., 1877 (Box 299)
      - Land titles, Cayuga County, N.Y., circa 1830-1870 (Box 299)
      - Patents
        - Barrels, 1875 (Box 299)
        - Fences, 1879-1881 (Box 299)
      - Retainer, 1867 (Box 299)
      - Title searches, 1870-1892 (Box 299)
    - Wright, D. and wife to Owasco Valley Oil Co.: Lease, Cayuga County, N.Y., 1865 (Box 299)
    - Wright, W.P.
      - Deeds, Putnam County, Fla.
        - to W. M. Bird, 1881 (Box 299)
        - to J. A. M. Varnum, 1875 (Box 299)
    - Wynne, R. P. to H.L. Victory: Mortgage, Oneida County, N.Y., 1899 (Box 299)
    - Young, McC.: Patent, Harvester, 1861 (Box 299)
  - Suits
    - Aiken and others v. New York & Oswego Railroad Co. and others, 1872 (Box 300)
    - Anderson v. Sterling Manufacturing Co., 1913 (Box 300)
    - Auburn National Bank v. Fisher, 1937 (Box 300)
    - Auburn National Bank v. New York, 1885 (Box 300)
    - Barber v. Morgan, undated (Box 300)
    - Bartlett v. Osborne and Wood, 1860-1869 (Box 300)
    - Beardsley v. Curtis, 1871 (Box 300)
    - Beardsley v. Finch, 1827-1840 (Box 300)
    - Bradley v. Bradley and others, 1839 (Box 300)
    - Brinkerhoff v. East Genesee Street & Seward Avenue Railway, 1867-1874 (Box 300)
    - Brown v. Town of Lansing (Tompkins County, N.Y.), 1874-1876 (Box 300)
    - Citizens' Light & Power Co. v. Burgess and others, 1901 (Box 300)
    - Clark v. Lawrence, 1843 (Box 300)
    - Coffin v. Frost, 1845 (Box 300)
    - Comstock v. Pettit and others, 1845 (Box 300)
    - Cornwell v. Curtis, 1873 (Box 300)
    - Cowan v. Osborne, 1871-1872 (Box 300)
    - Cowing v. Rumsey, 1868-1871 (Box 300)
    - Day v. Osborne, 1905 (Box 300)
    - Delaware & Hudson Company v. Public Service Commission, 1909 (Box 300)
    - DeWolf v. Morgan, 1865-1872 (Box 300)
    - Dorsey Revolving Harvester Rake Co. v. Herbert, circa 1874 (Box 300)
    - Dorsey Revolving Harvester Rake Co. v. Marsh and others, 1870-1874 (Box 301)
    - Dorsey Revolving Harvester Rake Co. v. Osborne and others, 1871-1874 (Box 301)
    - Doty v. Osborne, 1869 (Box 301)
    - Duffy v. Osborne, 1918-1921 (Box 301)
    - Fallbrook Coal Co. v. Curtis, 1871 (Box 301)
    - Finn v. Munger, 1840 (Box 301)
    - Flaherty v. Ross, 1912 (Box 301)
    - Franklin v. Park, 1823 (Box 301)
    - Graves v. New York, 1887 (Box 301)
    - Gwynn v. Osborne, 1924 (Box 301)
    - Hall and others v. Sheldon and others, 1874 (Box 301)
    - Hardenburgh and others v. East Genesee Street & Seward Avenue Railway, 1874 (Box 301)
    - Hart v. First National Bank of Groton, 1867 (Box 301)
    - Hart v. Hathaway and others, 1867-1868 (Box 301)
    - Hart v. Southern Central Railroad Co. and others, 1867 (Box 302)
    - Town of Hartwick v. Swarthout and others, undated (Box 302)
    - Hoopes v. Auburn Water Works Co., 1882 (Box 302)
    - Hunter v. Osborne, 1905-1924 (Box 302)
    - Kelly v. Eldred, 1881 (Box 302)
    - Keyes and others v. Munger, 1839-1840 (Box 302)
    - King and others v. Hudson, 1837-1843 (Box 302)
    - Kirby v. Harvey, 1831 (Box 302)
    - Kirby arnd Osborne v. Dodge & Stevenson Manufacturing Co., 1873 (Box 302)
    - Town of Lansing v. Lytle, circa 1902 (Box 302)
    - Lewis v. Auburn Publishing Co., 1913 (Box 302)
    - Luther, D. and others v. T. Luther and others, 1847 (Box 302)
    - McCabe v. Osborne, 1905 (Box 302)
    - Macomber v. Bradley, 1837 (Box 302)
    - McMaster & Co. v. Sing Sing Prison, 1848-1854 (Box 302)
    - Marsh and others v. Adriance and others, 1873 (Box 302)
    - Marsh and others v. Dodge and others, 1869-1873 (Box 302)
    - Middlesworth v. Jenkins, 1841 (Box 303)
    - Martin and Miller v. Brown, 1878 (Box 303)
    - Murphy v. Foote, 1860-1865 (Box 303)
    - New York v. Bartels and O'Hara, 1905 (Box 303)
    - New York v. Boada, 1917 (Box 303)
    - New York v. Cassidy and others, 1930 (Box 303)
    - New York v. Dunn, 1914-1915 (Box 303)
    - New York v. Kaplan (Vol. 179), 1915-1916 (Box 303)
    - New York v. Koerner (Vols. 180-181), 1897-1905; 2 volumes (Box 304)
    - New York v. Mercer, 1909-1916 (Box 304)
    - New York v. Ohlson, 1915 (Box 304)
    - New York v. Osborne, 1914-1916
      - Miscellaneous (Box 304)
      - Countersuits (Box 305)
      - Grand Jury Indictment (Box 305)
      - Interrogations (Box 305)
      - Jurors (Box 305)
      - Reports
        - Private investigations
          - February 1915 (Box 305)
          - March-April 1915, 4 folders (Box 306)
          - May-September 1915, 4 folders (Box 307)
        - Prison Commissioner's, and transcript of the testimony of witnesses (Box 307)
      - Statements
        - Defense (Box 307)
        - Witnesses
          - Miscellaneous (Box 307)
          - Alger, T. J. (Box 308)
          - Belden, E. H. (Box 308)
          - Brenner, S. (Box 308)
          - Broger, D. (Box 308)
          - Brooks, E. H. (Box 308)
          - Cass, E. P. (Box 308)
          - Clifford, M. (Box 308)
          - Cohen, A. (Box 308)
          - Connolly, J. (Box 308)
          - Cutler, J. (Box 308)
          - Daley, A. (Box 308)
          - DeLara, E. (Box 308)
          - Diedling, R. F. (Box 308)
          - Dillon, J. (Box 308)
          - Farr, C. W. (Box 308)
          - Fieseler, B. (Box 308)
          - Finnin, J. (Box 308)
          - Foreman, C. (Box 308)
          - Gandy, J.W. (Box 308)
          - Garfunkle, P. (Box 308)
          - Goldman, J. L. (Box 308)
          - Gwynn, C.A. (Box 308)
          - Harvey, J. (Box 308)
          - Hochwart, L. (Box 308)
          - Juffe, I. (Box 308)
          - Kessler, H. (Box 308)
          - Kiero, J. (Box 308)
          - Kleinberg, M. (Box 308)
          - Klugman, M. (Box 308)
          - Lipschitz, S. (Box 308)
          - McDonald, P.H. (Box 308)
          - McDonald, W.R. (Box 308)
          - Miller, S. (Box 308)
          - Milletello, F. (Box 309)
          - Myers, M. (Box 309)
          - Porter, R. (Box 309)
          - Resta, V. (Box 309)
          - Richards, F.W. (Box 309)
          - Rosen, S.J. (Box 309)
          - Steiglitz, E. (Box 309)
          - Stroock, S.M. (Box 309)
          - Thompson, W.B. (Box 309)
          - Vogel, P. (Box 309)
          - Welch, S. (Box 309)
          - Willit, W. (Box 309)
      - Transcript of testimony before Judge Tompkins (Box 309)
      - Trial (Vol. 182), 3 folders (Box 310)
      - Westchester County Grand Jury Minutes
        - Vol. I (Vol. 183) (Box 310)
        - Vols. II and III (Vols. 184-185), 2 volumes (Box 311)
        - Cross index (Box 312)
    - New York v. Platt, 1916 (Box 312)
    - Olmstead and others v. Stevens and others, 1871 (Box 312)
    - Osborne v. Auburn Telephone Co., 1904 (Box 312)
    - Osborne v. Banks, 1866 (Box 312)
    - Osborne v. Benjamin, 1877 (Box 312)
    - Osborne v. Carnes, 1924 (Box 312)
    - Osborne v. Curtis, 1871 (Box 312)
    - Osborne v. McManus, 1921 (Box 312)
    - Osborne v. New York Central Railroad, 1914 (Box 312)
    - Osborne v. Scollins, 1880 (Box 312)
    - Osborne v. Wills, 1924 (Box 312)
    - Osborne v. Withington, 1872 (Box 312)
    - Osborne and others v. Barber and others, 1869 (Box 312)
    - Osborne and others v. Sheldon and others, 1870-1874 (Box 312)
    - Osborne and others v. Snyder, 1860-1861 (Box 312)
    - Osborne and others v. Wells and others, 1872-1873 (Box 312)
    - Paddell v. City of New York, 1906 (Box 312)
    - Patty v. Osborne, 1872-1874 (Box 312)
    - Preston v. Southern Central Railroad Co., 1870-1871 (Box 312)
    - Price v. Allen and Turner, 1864 (Box 312)
    - Queen City Printing Co. v. Rochester Herald Co., 1925 (Box 312)
    - Rattigan v. O'Neill, 1911 (Box 312)
    - Remer v. Smith and others, 1839 (Box 312)
    - Richardson v. Osborne
      - [untitled], 1897 (Box 313)
      - Appeal (Vols. 186-187), 1898 (Box 313)
    - Roberts v. Barber and others, 1849 (Box 313)
    - Rumsey v. Cowing, 1868-1871 (Box 313)
    - Sartakoff v. John Hunter Corporation and others, 1919 (Box 314)
    - Selover v. Post, 1859 (Box 314)
    - Shaver v. Eldred, 1885 (Box 314)
    - Shirner v. Babbitt, 1878 (Box 314)
    - Shirner v. Mosher, 1878 (Box 314)
    - Smith v. City of Auburn, 1901 (Box 314)
    - Southern Central Railroad Co. v. Bradley, 1869 (Box 314)
    - Southern Central Railroad Co. v. Dodge, 1868 (Box 314)
    - Southern Central Railroad Co. v. Easterly, 1869 (Box 314)
    - Southern Central Railroad Co. v. Hutchinson, 1868-1869 (Box 314)
    - Southern Central Railroad Co. v. Lewis, 1868 (Box 314)
    - Southern Central Railroad Co. v. Parker, 1870 (Box 314)
    - Southern Central Railroad Co. v. Reynolds, 1871 (Box 314)
    - Swan v. Mowry and others, 1843 (Box 314)
    - Townsend and Fleming v. Osborne, 1912 (Box 314)
    - Treat v. Treat, undated (Box 314)
    - United States v. Osborne, 1925 (Box 314)
    - Town of Venice v. Murdock, 1875 (Box 314)